Guide to the Vassar College Archives Files, circa 1855-1969 (bulk 1860-1914)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Library — Librarian's Correspondence with President MacCracken, 1914 Oct - 1916 Dec (Box 5, Folder 4.16)
- Library — Librarian's Correspondence with President MacCracken, 1917 Apr-Jul (Box 5, Folder 4.17)
- Library — Librarian's Correspondence with President MacCracken, 1917 Jul - 1918 Mar (Box 5, Folder 4.18)
- Library — Librarian's Correspondence with President MacCracken, 1918 Apr-Nov (Box 5, Folder 4.19)
- Library — Librarian's Correspondence with President MacCracken, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 4.20)
- Library — Librarian's Correspondence with President MacCracken, 1920 Feb - 1921 Apr (Box 5, Folder 4.21)
- Library — Librarian's Correspondence with President MacCracken, 1921 May - 1922 Dec (Box 5, Folder 4.22)
- Library — Librarian's Correspondence with President MacCracken, 1923 Jan-Aug (Box 5, Folder 4.23)
- Library — Librarian's Correspondence with President MacCracken, 1923 Oct - 1924 Jan (Box 5, Folder 4.24)
- Library — Librarian's Correspondence with President MacCracken, 1924 Feb-Jun (Box 5, Folder 4.25)
- Library — Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 4.26)
- Library — Book Recommendations, 1866-1868 (Box 5, Folder 4.27)
- Lord Electric Company — Letter to W. H. Boughton regarding a financial settlement, 1914 Oct 15 (Box 15, Folder 9.13)
- Lyon, Joseph B. — Bequests to the College (Box 5, Folder 4.28)
- MacCracken, Henry Noble — Resignation and Re-Appointment, correspondence between trustees and administration, 1918 Sep (Box 15, Folder 9.14)
- MacCracken, Henry Noble — Resignation and Re-Appointment, correspondence between trustees and administration, 1918 Oct (Box 15, Folder 9.15)
- MacCracken, Henry Noble — Resignation and Re-Appointment, correspondence between trustees and administration, circa 1918 Sep-Oct (Box 15, Folder 9.16)
- MacCracken, Henry Noble — Resignation and Re-Appointment, correspondence between trustees and administration, 1918 Nov (Box 15, Folder 9.17)
- MacCracken, Henry Noble — Resignation and Re-Appointment, correspondence between trustees and administration, 1919 May-Sep (Box 15, Folder 9.18)
- Main Building — Construction - Bids on Construction, furnishing, equipping, etc., 1860 (Box 5, Folder 4.29)
- Main Building — Construction - Breaking Ground, 1861 (Box 5, Folder 4.30)
- Main Building — Construction - Addition Specifications and Contract, 1872 (Box 5, Folder 4.31)
- Main Building — Construction - Front Steps, 1865 (Box 5, Folder 4.32)
- Main Building — Construction - Heating System, 1862, 1864-1865 (Box 5, Folder 4.33)
- Main Building — Construction - Hot Water Tank, 1865 (Box 5, Folder 4.34)
- Main Building — Construction - Iron Doors, Gates, Railing, 1863, 1865 (Box 5, Folder 4.35)
- Main Building — Construction - Kitchen and Laundry, circa 1865 (Box 5, Folder 4.36)
- Main Building — Construction - Lightning Rods, 1865 (Box 5, Folder 4.37)
- Main Building — Construction - Miscellaneous, 1861, 1864-1865 (Box 5, Folder 4.38)
- Main Building — Construction - Name Tablet, 1862 (Box 5, Folder 4.39)
- Main Building — Construction - Plumbing, 1864; [SEE ALSO: Swan, Cyrus] (Box 5, Folder 4.40)
- Main Building — Construction - Refrigerator Room Smith's Plan, undated (Box 5, Folder 4.41)
- Main Building — Construction - Repairs and Improvements, 1866 (Box 5, Folder 4.42)
- Main Building— Contracts with William Harloe (builder) - Accounting of Work Estimates, 1864 (Box 5, Folder 4.43)
- Main Building — Contracts with William Harloe (builder) - Contract and Amended Contract, 1861-1862 (Box 5, Folder 4.44)
- Main Building — Contracts with William Harloe (builder) - Contract and Amended Contract, 1861-1862 (Box 5, Folder 4.45)
- Main Building — Contracts with William Harloe (builder) - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 4.46)
- Main Building — Contracts with William Harloe (builder) - Executed Contracts and Releases (Box 5, Folder 4.47)
- Main Building — Contracts with William Harloe (builder) - Work Estimates, #1 – 10, 1861-1862 (Box 5, Folder 4.48)
- Main Building — Contracts with William Harloe (builder) - Work Estimates, #11 – 20, 1862-1863 (Box 5, Folder 4.49)
- Main Building — Contracts with William Harloe (builder) - Work Estimates, #21, 23, 25-32, 1863-1864 (Box 5, Folder 4.50)
- Main Building — Contracts with James Renwick (architect) - Approval by Tufts and Coffin (Boston) of Renwick plans, 1861 (Box 5, Folder 4.51)
- Main Building — Contracts with James Renwick (architect) - Architectural Renderings and Drawings [SEE: Frances Lehman Loeb Art Center Collections]
- Main Building — Contracts with James Renwick (architect) - Contracts and Agreements, 1860-1864 (Box 5, Folder 4.52)
- Main Building — Contracts with James Renwick (architect) - Correspondence, 1861-1862, 1864 (Box 5, Folder 4.53)
- Main Building — Contracts with James Renwick (architect) - Design 1882 removed from Vassar Papers (Box 5, Folder 4.54)
- Main Building — Equipment and Furnishings - Chemical Equipment: Correspondence and Receipts 1864 [Purchased by R.A. Fisher, Professor of Chemistry in Paris] (Box 5, Folder 4.55)
- Main Building — Equipment and Furnishings - Clock, 1865 (Box 5, Folder 4.56)
- Main Building — Equipment and Furnishings - Furniture, Bedding, Carpets, 1863-1865 (Box 5, Folder 4.57)
- Main Building — Equipment and Furnishings - Lighting Fixtures, 1864 (Box 5, Folder 4.58)
- Main Building — Equipment and Furnishings - Organ Specifications, 1881 (Box 5, Folder 4.59)
- Main Building — Equipment and Furnishings - Pianos, 1865 (Box 5, Folder 4.60)
- Main Building — Floor Plan Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 4.61)
- Main Building — Insurance (Box 5, Folder 4.62)
- Main Building — Landscaping (Box 5, Folder 4.63)
- Mathematics, Natural Philosophy, and Chemistry Department — Reports, 1865-1874 (Box 5, Folder 4.64)
- Mathematics, Natural Philosophy, Physics — Applications: A-L (Box 5, Folder 4.65)
- Mathematics, Natural Philosophy, Physics — Applications: R-S (Box 5, Folder 4.66)
- Mathematics Department — Reports, 1874-1891 (Box 5, Folder 4.67)
- Mathematics Department — Reports, 1891-1895 (Box 5, Folder 4.68)
- Mathematics Department — Reports, 1895-1900 (Box 5, Folder 4.69)
- Mathematics Department — Reports, 1900-1914 (Box 5, Folder 4.70)
- The Mercer Company — Invoice for furniture paid by VC Trustees, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 9.19)
- Miscellaneous Notes — Visitors 1868, number of students, messenger wages, commencement invitations, number of books in library (Box 5, Folder 4.71)
- Monnier, Mathilda (VC faculty) — Letter from Major General H. P. McCain to Henry Noble MacCracken about Monnier's work in the Y.M.C.A. Canteen Unit, 1918 Oct 10 (Box 15, Folder 9.20)
- Mortgages, 1861-1910 (Box 5, Folder 4.72)
- Mortgages — Vassar Female College to Matthew Vassar, 1866 Nov - 1868 Oct (Box 5, Folder 4.73)
- Museum — Reports, 1902-1904, 1910-1912 (Box 5, Folder 4.74)
- Music Department — Programs, 1867-1891 (Box 5, Folder 4.75)
- Music Department — Reports, 1864-1885 (Box 5, Folder 4.76)
- Music Department — Reports, 1884-1902 (Box 5, Folder 4.77)
- Music Department — Reports, 1902-1913, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 4.78)
- Music Department — Applications from Professors: Music, 1860-1864 (Box 5, Folder 4.79)
- Natural History Department — Reports, 1865-1873, 1876-1879 (Box 6, Folder 4.80)
- Natural History Department — Reports, 1879-1887 (Box 6, Folder 4.81)
- Natural History Department — Reports, 1887-1891 (Box 6, Folder 4.82)
- Natural History Department — Catalog of Cabinet, agreements, documents, and correspondence (Box 6, Folder 4.83)
- Natural History Department — Nationalist Catalogue of Cabinet of Mineralogy and Geology, correspondence W/ Henry A. Ward, etc., 1873 (Box 6, Folder 4.84)
- Natural History Department — Orton, James (Faculty), 1869-1877 (Box 6, Folder 4.88)
- Nettleton, George H. — Guest book during Nettleton's tenure as acting VC President, 1922 Fall (Box 15, Folder 9.21)
- Observatory — Advertisement, 1886 (Box 6, Folder 4.85)
- Observatory — Contract, 1863 (Box 6, Folder 4.86)
- Observatory — Construction, 1863-1865 (Box 6, Folder 4.87)
- Pecuniary Aid Students (Box 6, Folder 4.89)
- Philalethean Society, 1866-1869 (Box 6, Folder 4.90)
- Philalethean Society, 1870-1873 (Box 6, Folder 4.91)
- Philalethean Society, 1891-1894, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 4.92)
- Philalethean Society, 1910-1911, 1914, undated (Box 6, Folder 4.93)
- Philosophy Department — Applications, 1864-1865 (Box 6, Folder 4.94)
- Philosophy Department — Reports [includes Ethics and Mental and Moral Philosophy], 1886, 1871, 1887-1902 (Box 6, Folder 4.95)
- Philosophy Department — Reports, 1903-1914 (Box 6, Folder 4.96)
- Physical Training Department — Reports [includes gymnastics], 1866-1879 (Box 6, Folder 4.97)
- Physical Training Department — Reports [includes gymnastics], 1890-1899 (Box 6, Folder 4.98)
- Physical Training Department — Reports [includes gymnastics], 1899-1908 (Box 6, Folder 4.99)
- Physical Training Department — Reports [includes gymnastics], 1908-1914 (Box 6, Folder 4.100)
- Physician — SEE ALSO: Physiology and Hygiene
- Physician — Reports, 1870-1873, 1882-1886 (Box 6, Folder 4.101)
- Physician — Reports, 1886-1892 (Box 6, Folder 4.102)
- Physician — Reports, 1892-1897 (Box 6, Folder 4.103)
- Physician — Reports, 1898-1901 (Box 6, Folder 4.104)
- Physician — Reports, 1901-1904 (Box 6, Folder 4.105)
- Physician — Reports, 1904-1907 (Box 6, Folder 4.106)
- Physician — Reports, 1907-1910 (Box 6, Folder 4.107)
- Physician — Reports, 1910-1912 (Box 6, Folder 4.108)
- Physician — Reports, 1912-1914 (Box 6, Folder 4.109)
- Physician — Reports, 1916-1917, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 4.110)
- Physician — Reports, 1923-1926 (Box 6, Folder 4.111)
- Physician — Reports, 1926-1929 (Box 6, Folder 4.112)
- Physics Department — Reports [includes Chemistry], 1874-1884, 1885-1889 (Box 6, Folder 5.1)
- Physics Department — Reports [includes Chemistry], 1889-1894 (Box 6, Folder 5.2)
- Physics Department — Reports, 1894-1905 (Box 6, Folder 5.3)
- Physics Department — Reports, 1905-1914 (Box 6, Folder 5.4)
- Physiology and Hygiene Department — Reports, 1865-1871 (Box 6, Folder 5.5)
- Physiology and Hygiene Department — Reports, 1871-1879 (Box 6, Folder 5.6)
- Physiology and Hygiene Department — Reports, 1879-1882, 1887-1896 (Box 6, Folder 5.7)
- Physiology and Hygiene Department — Reports, 1896, 1898-1907 (Box 6, Folder 5.8)
- Physiology and Hygiene Department — Reports, 1907-1914 (Box 6, Folder 5.9)
- Physiology and Hygiene Department — Gymnastics Applications, 1863-1865 (Box 6, Folder 5.10)
- Poole, William F. — Letters to and from Vassar presidents regarding work he did for the college, 1865 (Box 15, Folder 9.22)
- Porter, T. H. — Letter re: Appointment to Professor of Rhetoric and English, 1865 (Box 6, Folder 5.11)
- Postal Service, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 5.12)
- Poughkeepsie City Railroad Co. — Agreement with Vassar College, 1872 (Box 6, Folder 5.13)
- Preachers — List of preachers who spoke at Vassar, 1870, 1886-1915 (Box 6, Folder 5.14)
- Presidents — General Orders from President, 1869-1891, 1902 (Box 6, Folder 5.15)
- Presidents — Reports [Raymond], 1865-1869 (Box 6, Folder 5.16)
- Presidents — Reports [Raymond], 1869-1872 (Box 6, Folder 5.17)
- Presidents — Reports [Raymond], 1872-1874 (Box 6, Folder 5.18)
- Presidents — Reports [Raymond], 1874-1877 (Box 6, Folder 5.19)
- Presidents — Report [Raymond], 1877 (Box 7, Folder 5.20)
- Presidents — Reports [Caldwell], 1878-1880 (Box 7, Folder 5.21)
- Presidents — Report [Caldwell], 1880-1882 (Box 7, Folder 5.22)
- Presidents — Report [Caldwell], 1882 (Box 7, Folder 5.23)
- Presidents — Report [Caldwell], 1883 (Box 7, Folder 5.24)
- Presidents — Report [Caldwell], 1884 (Box 7, Folder 5.25)
- Presidents — Baccalaureate Sermon by President Caldwell, 1881 Jun 19 (Box 7, Folder 5.26)
- Presidents — Kendrick Report, 1885 (Box 7, Folder 5.27)
- Presidents — Reports [Taylor], 1886-1892 (Box 7, Folder 5.28)
- Presidents — Reports [Taylor], 1892-1896 (Box 7, Folder 5.29)
- Presidents — Reports [Taylor], 1896-1899 (Box 7, Folder 5.30)
- Presidents — Reports [Taylor], 1899-1902 (Box 7, Folder 5.31)
- Presidents — Reports [Taylor], 1902-1905 (Box 7, Folder 5.32)
- Presidents — Reports [Taylor], 1905-1907 (Box 7, Folder 5.33)
- Presidents — Reports [Taylor], 1907-1909 (Box 7, Folder 5.34)
- Presidents — Report [Taylor], 1909 (Box 7, Folder 5.35)
- Presidents — Report [Taylor], 1910 (Box 7, Folder 5.36)
- Presidents — Reports [Taylor], 1911-1914 (Box 7, Folder 5.37)
- Presidents — Reports, 1865-1885; [transcriptions] (Box 7, Folder 5.37a)
- Presidents — Reports, 1886-1903, 1905-1907, 1914; [transcriptions] (Box 7, Folder 5.37b)
- Presidents — Taylor Report on Internal Management and Organization, 1904-1909 (Box 7, Folder 5.38)
- Presidents — Reports [MacCracken], 1916-1920 (Box 7, Folder 5.39)
- Presidents — Powers of: On President's Right to Vote Twice, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 5.40)
- Psychology Department — SEE ALSO: Philosophy, Mental and Moral
- Psychology Department — Reports, 1907-1914 (Box 7, Folder 5.41)
- Randall's Island, Sing-Sing, and Vassar College — Clippings, notes, and correspondence re: a proposed Boys' Reformatory near VC, 1907 (Box 7, Folder 5.42)
- Randall's Island, Sing-Sing, and Vassar College — Clippings, notes, and correspondence re: a proposed Boys' Reformatory near VC, 1908 Jan (Box 7, Folder 5.43)
- Randall's Island, Sing-Sing, and Vassar College — Clippings, notes, and correspondence re: a proposed Boys' Reformatory near VC, 1908 Feb (Box 7, Folder 5.44)
- Randall's Island, Sing-Sing, and Vassar College — Clippings, notes, and correspondence re: a proposed Boys' Reformatory near VC, 1908 Apr, undated (Box 7, Folder 5.45)
- Raymond, J. H. — Letter from Morgan Smith, 1876 Mar 1 (Box 15, Folder 9.23)
- Raymond Reading Room (Box 7, Folder 5.46)
- Real Estate Holdings — Low Property Deeds (Box 7, Folder 5.47)
- Real Estate Holdings — Kansas (Box 7, Folder 5.48)
- Real Estate Holdings — New York City (Box 7, Folder 5.49)
- Real Estate Holdings — New York State (Box 7, Folder 5.50)
- Real Estate Holdings — Steuben County, NY (Box 7, Folder 5.51)
- Religion (Box 7, Folder 5.52)
- Richardson, Sophia F. (VC 1879) — Letters, mostly to Mrs. O. V. Stewart, regarding raising funds for the endowment of Sophia Richardson's grave, 1916-1923 (Box 15, Folder 9.24)
- Riding School (Box 7, Folder 5.53)
- Riding School — Contracts (Box 7, Folder 5.54)
- Rockefeller Hall (Box 7, Folder 5.55)
- Romance Languages Department — SEE ALSO: French Department
- Romance Languages Department — Reports, 1895-1901 (Box 7, Folder 5.56)
- Romance Languages Department — Reports, [1901]-1907 (Box 7, Folder 5.57)
- Romance Languages Department — Reports, 1907-1914 (Box 7, Folder 5.58)
- Rombout Deed — SEE: Matthew Vassar Papers, Box 24
- Salmon, Lucy M. — Announcement of celebrations related to the 400th anniversary of the birth of John Calvin, 1909 Mar 23 (Box 15, Folder 9.25)
- Salmon, Lucy M. — Letter to Mr. Pelton regarding a meeting with Dr. Stulz, 1914 Nov 6 (Box 15, Folder 9.26)
- Salmon, Lucy M. — Letters from James Thorne Harper regarding book acquisitions, 1888; [typescript, copies] (Box 15, Folder 9.27)
- Scholarships (Box 7, Folder 5.59)
- Scholarships — R. H. McDonald, circulars and draft contract, 1877 (Box 15, Folder 9.28)
- Scholarships — Adolph Sutro Scholarship, 1913 Dec 13 (Box 15, Folder 9.29)
- Schou, J.N. (Box 7, Folder 5.60)
- [Secretary of the College] — College Journal, 1870-1871 (Box 7, Folder 5.61)
- Secretary of the College — Reports [Swan], 1862, 1867 (Box 7, Folder 5.62)
- Secretary of the College — Contracts, rules, correspondence [Swan], 1866, undated (Box 7, Folder 5.63)
- Secretary of the College — Reports [McCaleb], 1900-1913 (Box 7, Folder 5.64)
- Sewer (Box 8, Folders 5.65-5.68)
- Sheldon, Smith (Bookseller) — Letters to his brother and Nathan Bishop; letter from Benson J. Lossing, 1869-1870 (Box 15, Folder 9.30)
- Steward's Office — Accounting Records, 1865 (Box 8, Folder 5.69)
- Steward's Office — Applications for Position of Steward, 1862-1865 (Box 8, Folder 5.70)
- Steward's Office — Contract for Employment of William Smith, 1864 (Box 8, Folder 5.71)
- Steward's Office — Correspondence w/ General Superintendent Cyrus Swan, 1865 Jul-Nov (Box 8, Folder 5.72)
- Steward's Office — Correspondence w/ General Superintendent Cyrus Swan, 1865 Dec - 1866 July (Box 8, Folder 5.73)
- Steward's Office — Correspondence w/ Harriet Terry, Lady Principal, 1872 (Box 8, Folder 5.74)
- Steward's Office — Correspondence w/ V.C. Trustees, 1864-1865 (Box 8, Folder 5.75)
- Steward's Office — Inventories, 1865-1866 (Box 8, Folder 5.76)
- Steward's Office — Letterbook, 1865-1866 (Box 8, Folder 5.77)
- Steward's Office — Meal Menus, 1865-1866 (Box 8, Folder 5.78)
- Steward's Office — Reports, 1865-1866, undated (Box 8, Folder 5.79)
- Stocks and Bonds (Securities) (Box 8, Folder 5.80)
- Strong House — Contract Agreement for Dormitory (1892), 1884-1902; [SEE ALSO: Folder 2.59a, Expense Accounts and Estimates [Notebook], pp.64-69] (Box 8, Folder 5.81)
- Student Religious Association (Box 8, Folder 5.82)
- Students — Constitutions of the Classes of 1897, 1900, 1902-1904, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 5.83)
- Students — Constitutions of the Classes of 1876-1879, 1881-1886, 1894-1896 (Box 8, Folder 5.84)
- Students — Constitutions of the Societies and Clubs: A - C (Box 8, Folder 5.85)
- Students — Constitutions of the Societies and Clubs: D - L (Box 8, Folder 5.86)
- Students — Constitutions of the Societies and Clubs: M - P (Box 8, Folder 5.87)
- Students — Constitutions of the Societies and Clubs: Q - Z (Box 8, Folder 5.88)
- Students — Students Debates on Enrollment, Scholarships, Plays, Requirements for Admission (Box 8, Folder 5.89)
- Students — Students' Expenses (Box 8, Folder 5.90)
- Students — Students' Fees (Receipts) (Box 8, Folder 5.91)
- Students — Students' Grades. Grade and Studybook ["Times Tables"], 1865-1866 (Box 14)
- Students — Students' Grades. Grade and Studybook, 1868-1869 (Box 8, Folder 5.91A)
- Students — Students' Grades. Grade and Studybook, 1869-1870 (Box 8, Folder 5.91B)
- Students — Students' Grades. Grade and Studybook ["Times Tables/Courses Taken"], 1889-1890 (Box 14)
- Students — Students' Petition to the Faculty for Various Organizations (Box 8, Folder 6.1)
- Students — Students' Rooms (Box 8, Folder 6.2)
- Students — Students' Applications for M.A., 1884-1902 (Box 8, Folder 6.3)
- Students — Students' Applications for M.A. (Box 8, Folder 6.4)
- Students — Students' Applications for M.A., A - K (Box 8, Folder 6.5)
- Students — Students' M.A. Degree work on, L - R (Box 8, Folder 6.6)
- Students — Students' M.A. Degree work on, S - Z (Box 8, Folder 6.7)
- Students' Association (Box 8, Folder 6.8)
- Students' Association — Constitution (Box 8, Folder 6.9)
- Students' Association — Constitution and By-Laws (Box 8, Folder 6.10)
- Students' Association — 1914-1924, Documents, Letters (Box 8, Folder 6.11)
- Students' Association — 1914-1924, Documents, Letters (Box 8, Folder 6.12)
- Students' Association — Report (Box 8, Folder 6.13)
- Students' Association — Rules (Box 8, Folder 6.14)
- Students' Association — Self-Government Committee, 1889-1906 (Box 8, Folder 6.15)
- Students' Building (Box 8, Folder 6.16)
- Swan, Cyrus — Correspondence, 1864-1866 (Box 9, Folder 6.17)
- Swan, Cyrus — Notes and Suggestions, 1865, undated (Box 9, Folder 6.18)
- Swan, Cyrus — Correspondence from Charles A. Raymond, 1864 (Box 9, Folder 6.19)
- Swan, Cyrus — miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 6.20)
- Taylor, James M. — Correspondence with Augustus W. Cowles (President of Elmira College); clippings related to Elmira College, 1890 (Box 15, Folder 9.31)
- Taylor, James M. — Resolution of the Republican National Convention on the integrity of the court system, 1908 Jun 6 (Box 15, Folder 9.32)
- Taylor Hall (Box 9, Folder 6.21)
- Taxes — Taxation Exemption (Box 9, Folder 6.22)
- Taxes (Box 9, Folder 6.23)
- Telephone Service, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 6.24)
- Thompson, C. Mildred — Letter to Herbert Gurney (VC Treasurer), 1918 Oct 19 (Box 15, Folder 9.33)
- Thompson, Frederick Ferns (Box 9, Folder 6.25)
- Torrey, H. W. — Letter nominating Dr. Peabody as a Vassar College Trustee, 1880 Apr 19 (Box 15, Folder 9.34)
- Townson, Andrew J. — Memorial draft, 1920 Jun 7 (Box 15, Folder 9.35)
- Treasurer — Bankbook, 1865-1866 (Box 9, Folder 6.26)
- Treasurer — Cancelled Checks, 1861-1862 (Box 9, Folder 6.27)
- Treasurer — Cancelled Checks, 1862-1863 (Box 9, Folder 6.28)
- Treasurer — Cancelled Checks, 1863-1864 (Box 9, Folder 6.29)
- Treasurer — Cancelled Notes, 1865-1869 (incomplete) (Box 9, Folder 6.30)
- Treasurer — Cancelled Notes, 1869-1883 (Box 9, Folder 6.31)
- Treasurer — Funds (Vassar will), 1889 (Box 9, Folder 6.32)
- Treasurer — Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 6.33)
- Treasurer — Pay Roll, March, 1872, 1900 (Box 9, Folder 6.34)
- Treasurer — Receipts, William Harloe, 1861-1862 (Box 9, Folder 6.35)
- Treasurer — Receipts, William Harloe, 1862-1863 (Box 9, Folder 6.36)
- Treasurer — Receipts, William Harloe, 1863-1864 (Box 9, Folder 6.37)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1861-1862 (Box 9, Folder 6.38)
- Treasurer — Receipts, Matthew Vassar and VC Building Account, 1861-1862 (Box 9, Folder 6.39)
- Treasurer — Receipts, VC General Expense Account, 1861-1862 (Box 9, Folder 6.40)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1861-1862 (Box 9, Folder 6.41)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1862-1863 (Box 9, Folder 6.42)
- Treasurer — Receipts (General Expense Account), 1862-1863 (Box 9, Folder 6.43)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1862-1863 (Box 9, Folder 6.44)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1863-1864 (Box 9, Folder 6.45)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1863-1864 (Box 9, Folder 6.46)
- Treasurer — Receipts (General Expense Account), 1863-1864 (Box 9, Folder 6.47)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1863-1864 (Box 9, Folder 6.48)
- Treasurer — Receipts (Observatory), 1863-1864 (Box 9, Folder 6.49)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1871 Dec - 1872 Mar (Box 9, Folder 6.50)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1872 Apr (Box 9, Folder 6.51)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1872 May-Jun (Box 9, Folder 6.52)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 6.53)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1900s (Box 9, Folder 6.54)
- Treasurer — Elsworth, Edward (Box 9, Folder 6.55)
- Treasurer — Receipts, 1861 Jan-Jun (Box 9, Folder 6.56)
- Treasurer — Report, 1861-1862 (Box 9, Folder 6.57)
- Treasurer — Report, 1862-1863 (Box 9, Folder 6.58)
- Treasurer — Report, 1863-1864 (Box 9, Folder 6.59)
- Treasurer — Report, 1864-1865 (Box 9, Folder 6.60)
- Treasurer — Report, 1865-1866 (Box 9, Folder 6.61)
- Treasurer — Report, 1866-1867 (Box 9, Folder 6.62)
- Treasurer — Report, 1867-1868 (Box 9, Folder 6.63)
- Treasurer — Report, 1868-1869 (Box 9, Folder 6.64)
- Treasurer — Report, 1869-1870 (Box 9, Folder 6.65)
- Treasurer — Report, 1870-1871 (Box 9, Folder 6.66)
- Treasurer — Report (scattered annual and special reports), 1870-1875 (Box 9, Folder 6.67)
- Treasurer — Report (scattered annual and special reports), 1878-1905 (Box 9, Folder 6.68)
- Treasurer — Report (scattered annual and special reports), 1906-1915 (Box 9, Folder 6.69)
- Treasurer — Report (scattered annual and special reports), 1917-1922 (Box 9, Folder 6.70)
- Trustees — Acceptances of First Trustees, 1861 (Box 9, Folder 6.71)
- Trustees — Autograph (Box 9, Folder 6.72)
- Trustees — By-Laws (Box 9, Folder 6.73)
- Trustees — Charter of Vassar College with the Will of its Founder (Box 9, Folder 6.74)
- Trustees — Committees Lists (Box 10, Folder 6.75)
- Trustees — Committees Common Age of Trustees (Box 10, Folder 6.76)
- Trustees — Committees Art Gallery. Report (includes letters to Art Committee), 1861, 1869-1882 (Box 10, Folder 6.77)
- Trustees — Committees Art Gallery. Report (includes letters to Art Committee), 1889-1893 (Box 10, Folder 6.78)
- Trustees — Committees By-Laws (Box 10, Folder 6.79)
- Trustees — Cabinets and Apparatus Report (1), 1861-1871 (Box 10, Folder 6.80)